quiz_questions = [
    {
        "question": "What make is the car in which Marty Mcfly uses too\n"
        "travel back in time?\n\n",
        "answers": ["B.M.W", "DMC Delorian", "Ford"],
        "correct": "DMC Delorian"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to Doctor Emmit Brown what makes\n"
        "time travel possible?\n\n",
        "answers": ["The rotation of the earth ",
                    "Newtons law of motion",
                    "The flux capacitor"],
        "correct": "The flux capacitor"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much power does the time machine need\n"
        "to send Marty back in time?\n\n",
        "answers": ["1.21 gigawatts", "2000 megawatts", "55 volts"],
        "correct": "1.21 gigawatts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What date does Marty Mcfly travel back too?\n\n",
        "answers": ["September 26th 1989",
                    "November 5th 1955",
                    "December 25th 1965"],
        "correct": "November 5th 1955"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the dance Marty attends where\n"
        "his mom and dad kiss for the first time?\n\n",
        "answers": ["The fish under the sea dance",
                    "The monkey in the jungle dance",
                    "The enchantment under the sea dance"],
        "correct": "The enchantment under the sea dance"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the mail Marty meets\n"
        "Doctor Emmit Brown called?\n\n",
        "answers": ["twin pine mall",
                    "lonley pine mall",
                    "westfilds"],
        "correct": "twin pine mall"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what time does the lightning strike the\n"
        "clock tower?\n\n",
        "answers": ["12:00pm",
                    "10:50am",
                    "10:04pm"],
        "correct": "10:04pm"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the mayor in Marty's time?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Mayor Goldburge Jenson",
                    "Mayor Goldie Wilson",
                    "Mayor Biff Tannan"],
        "correct": "Mayor Goldie Wilson"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the main antaganist?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Geff Bazos",
                    "Biff Tannan",
                    "George Mcfly"],
        "correct": "Biff Tannan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the town Marty lives at?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Hill Vally",
                    "Springfield",
                    "Riverdale"],
        "correct": "Hill Vally"
    },
    {
        "question": "What song did Marty and his band play for\n"
        "the dance auditions?\n\n",
        "answers": ["I will do anything for love",
                    "Taninted love",
                    "Power of love"],
        "correct": "Power of love"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Doc Brown's dog in 1985?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Einstein",
                    "Tesla",
                    "Newton"],
        "correct": "Einstein"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Marty's band?\n\n",
        "answers": ["The Who",
                    "The Hill Vally Rockers",
                    "The Pinheads"],
        "correct": "The Pinheads"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color was Marty's Calvin Klein underwear?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Red",
                    "White",
                    "Purple"],
        "correct": "Purple"
    },
    {
        "question": "From whom did Doc obtain the plutonium he needed\n"
        "to use the time machine?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Russians",
                    "English",
                    "Lybians"],
        "correct": "Lybians"
    },
    {
        "question": "What speed does the Delorian need to reach to send\n"
        "someone back or forward in time?\n\n",
        "answers": ["77MPH", "78MPH", "88MPH"],
        "correct": "88MPH"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Doc Brown hit his head on when he invented\n"
        "the flux capacitor?\n\n",
        "answers": ["The cupbord door in his kitchen",
                    "The sink in his toilet",
                    "The bonnet on his car"],
        "correct": "The sink in his toilet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What phrase does the Doc repeat throughout\n"
        "the trilogy?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Great Scott!",
                    "Na-Nu Na-Nu Shazbot",
                    "Danger, Will Robinson"],
        "correct": "Great Scott!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Marty's girlfriend\n"
        "in Back to the Future?\n\n",
        "answers": ["Jennifer",
                    "Alison",
                    "Betty"],
        "correct": "Jennifer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Marty's dads motto once he\n"
        "returns back from the past?\n\n",
        "answers": ["With great power comes great responsabilty",
                    "You put your mind to it you can accomplish anything",
                    "Justice delayed is justice denied."],
        "correct": "You put your mind to it you can accomplish anything"
    }
]
